My friend Barry
I'm telling you,
that creature's fooling us.
There are still traces.
We won't be fooled any longer.
Give me the goat.
Here.
Not like that!
Why not like that?
Not like this.
-Sideways!
-The wolf doesn't care!
Are you kidding me?
We'll catch him this time!
We got him!
You're hungry too, aren't you?
Come!
-I'm coming!
-We got him!
Goddammit!
Impossible!
Come on!
That's enough!
Come. Enough is enough!
Where have you been?
I was worried.
I fought a wolf!
Yeah, right...
Sure!
And I even won!
Tomorrow will be another tough day.
Can't we rest a little longer here?
Come on, we're almost there.
One more day until we reach the pass,
then another day or two
on the other side into the valley.
And then we're at the sea.
Then we're in Italy.
Where it's warm.
There are no soldiers there?
No French people, that's for sure.
And if they do show up,
the Austrians will kick their asses!
Good.
We'll find work.
The rich people in the big cities
-need servants.
-Servants?
Yes.
We're getting our own room.
Just for the two of us.
A real bed.
And you...
You'll even get a new scarf.
Tell me about the sea.
It's bigger than where we live, right?
Bigger than Lake Lucerne.
A hundred times bigger.
So big
that you can't see the other shore.
And there are fish
as big as calves...
And it's warm.
And when you lie on your back
and stretch out your arms,
the water will carry you all by itself.
We just have to get
over the pass tomorrow.
And then we'll have
a better life in Italy.
We can do it.
Come on!
Austrian soldiers.
What are they doing here?
Kick the asses of the French, right?
Are you okay?
We're almost there.
Alfons!
I can't go on anymore!
Let me see.
Finally!
Where am I?
In the hospice.
You slept for two days straight.
Where's Alfons?
I have to take you to the kitchen
as soon as you're awake.
You're awake now!
Put your clothes on.
I'll wait outside.
Come on now!
Did you try to steal again?
-You're getting fatter and fatter!
-Come, Patch, come.
Come.
The kitchen is this way.
-Hi.
-Hello, Resi.
This is my father.
His dogs are the best avalanche dogs
in the world.
They've saved many lives.
Come! I have to take you to the kitchen.
Hurry up before they do
something stupid.
Resi!
I need a new bandage.
Come in the afternoon.
Brother Medicus will be back then.
But it's already quite loose.
It won't heal properly like that.
This tiny cut?
Just leave alone,
then it'll heal by itself.
-Where's Alfons?
-Who?
Alfons, my brother.
-Hey!
-Great shot.
Come on, leave those monkeys alone.
Brother Pietro.
Hello, my dear!
He needs a warm soup.
Sure!
Go ahead, give it to him.
I don't have time.
A bowl of soup!
Resi is a lovely girl, but...
How do you say...
She's a stubborn girl.
What's your name?
George.
Sit down.
A good soup...
Here you go... enjoy!
Eat!
And then we'll see what we do with you.
I want to see my brother.
Your brother?
Yes.
We arrived two days ago.
What?
Your brother...
They all left for Italy.
Two days ago.
No!
Sonny!
Your soup...
Alfons!
You wanted to see me, Prior?
I'm supposed to be in the library.
That's the boy from the last trek.
His brother has
travelled on without him.
Where is he from?
Emmental.
Emmental, Prior.
His name is George.
I want to go to Italy.
To my brother.
They boy's crazy.
You can't cross the pass on your own.
I'll wait for the next trek.
This was the last
trek you travelled with.
Until spring.
Until spring?
That means...
-That means you're staying here
till the snow has melted.
What about your parents?
Your name is George, right?
George,
you'll make yourself useful here.
Brother Pietro is always happy
to have extra help.
Work never stops up here.
Is there any way to accommodate the boy?
-You mean... in the novices' quarters?
-Yes.
Heavens above...
There's no free bed?
Prior, with all due respect,
we can't put a farm boy with
the novices. It'll cause unrest.
Our discipline! How will
the parents and patrons react when...
I. I will find a place for him.
Fine.
George, you'll do the jobs given to you.
You help out where help is needed.
Okay?
Our job is to serve.
I expect diligence,
obedience and humility.
You will fit in while you are with us.
Do you understand that?
You guys are huge!
It's okay, I won't hurt you.
I've never seen such big,
beautiful dogs.
I won't hurt you.
Yes. Everything's fine.
What a lively bunch you are!
Hey, don't bite.
Hey, you.
You cheeky bugger!
What's wrong with you?
Is something wrong?
You're so weak!
Dad!
Voilà. Come!
Get out of there!
You can't sleep here.
And certainly not in the litter box.
Yes, Stella.
The mother can be very dangerous
if you get too close to her puppies.
Yes, I know
but it kept me warm.
This isn't a dormitory!
It's a stable.
Why isn't he drinking?
He can't fight for his place.
The others keep pushing him away
and he's getting weaker and weaker.
He probably won't survive.
Who gave you this ammonite?
It's a stone snail.
That's a fossil.
Of an animal that lived on earth
a long time ago.
It's a lucky charm.
Alfons gave it to me.
And it's a stone snail!
Where did they assign you to work?
With Brother Pietro.
You'll help me with the dogs,
when you're done in the kitchen.
George, right?
Julien.
Here you go, something delicious.
Not so fast!
Did you eat the scraps yourself?
Leave me alone!
Oh, thank you!
Can I take the boy along with me?
I'll bring him back, don't worry.
Alright.
George.
Come!
Go ahead!
You go on.
Me?
I have to peel onions?
Work is work.
Lord, help me.
Watch out!
You have to walk close to the wall here.
So, what happens with him now?
With whom?
With Stella's puppy
that's not getting any milk.
It won't survive.
And Stella will eat him.
Nature does what it has to do.
Enough talk.
Work is calling.
Come.
I'll bring him back, Stella.
I can't just let him die.
What on earth are you doing?
Why aren't you sleeping?
Get out of here!
How cute!
What are you doing
with him in my kitchen?
Julien says
that he's going to die.
Because nature does what it has to do.
Nature. Nature
doesn't know everything.
Wait a minute.
There!
Now take him back to the stable.
Thank you!
Come.
You need to drink.
I promised your mother
that you wouldn't die.
Here.
George?
Yes?
We have to get firewood.
-What! Now?
-Yes, now!
Brother Pietro will
get very angry if there
-isn't enough wood in the kitchen
tomorrow morning. -Okay.
What's the matter?
I'm coming.
I can't wait forever!
Let's try again later.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Matteo!
What are you doing?
You can't do that!
Let me out!
I have to get out of here! Hey!
You'd rather be
with the pigs in the barn, right?
But maybe they don't want you there.
Let me out!
Here you go, an onion.
Unpeeled.
In case you get hungry.
Hey!
Matteo!
Sorry.
You have to let me out.
Matteo!
I have to get out of here!
Let me out!
Wait!
Leave me alone.
Please don't tell on me!
You're still alive!
Go ahead, drink!
You're drinking. Great!
Sonny!
Where were you?
I'm sorry.
I overslept.
No!
Not in my kitchen!
No dawdling in my kitchen.
Got it?
Go!
Thank you.
What?
You stole it?
I helped him.
But Dad said...
Stella didn't eat him!
He was with you the whole time!
Wait! Where are you going?
I have to tell my dad.
Can't you...?
I have to feed him.
He's not strong enough yet.
Have you given him a name yet?
A name?
Yes, he needs a name.
What name would you like?
I didn't quite get that.
Brother Pietro would call him Piccolo.
In a few weeks, he'll be about this big.
And anyway,
the name must begin with a B.
B?
Why?
That's just the way it is.
Each litter needs to start with
a different initial letter.
The last puppies were called
Alma, Achim, Arno and Alva.
And now it's B's turn.
B... B...
How about Benno?
Boring!
Balthasar or...
Bartholomew.
Way too long, you can't shout that.
Balthasar!
Bartholomew!
More like... Flash.
Benedict?
Heavens above!
What do you think of Biter?
But he's not a biter, is he?
Bear?
What happens when a real bear shows up?
And we call for the dog...
What about... Barry?
Barry?
Yes, Barry.
Fearless Barry.
Barry the protector.
Barry!
Good morning, Barry.
Hello, Barry.
Did you sleep well?
You have to be very quiet.
No one must discover you.
Okay?
I'll be back.
You can't come with me, Barry.
You have to stay here.
I haven't got time right now.
Stay here and wait, okay?
I'll be back soon.
That's my book! Give it back.
It was under the desk.
Did I allow you to touch it
with your dirty fingers?
Do you smell it too?
And do you know what it is?
You can't see it,
but you can smell it.
When you grow up with it,
it sticks to you.
You'll always be a country bumpkin
who stinks of cow dung.
And no book in the world
will ever change that!
Italy.
Does this lead south?
Yes, when the snow has melted.
Have you ever been there, in Italy?
I came to Italy across the sea.
From Africa.
And why are you up here?
I got a job at the hospice.
No one up here has a problem
if your fur isn't white.
Like with the dogs.
It's the work that counts.
Did you ever want to go back?
Home?
We've found a place here.
Resi and I.
If you're lucky,
you will find yours too.
Let's go!
At these stone towers
travellers can get their bearings.
I thought the pass was closed?
It is!
A... A... Abor... Montal...
Are you reading to Barry?
Hey, Barry.
I'm sure he likes it.
Even though he can probably read better
than you.
As if you could read.
The streets are so clean
that women walk there all year round
in slippers.
There are two rows of trees
planted on both sides of the canals.
Did you never go to school?
There's no teacher in our village.
Sometimes
the pastor taught us something
when there wasn't much work to do
on the farms in winter.
Come on, I'll show you.
It's easier if you memorise
the words as images.
That's how I did it.
If you want to travel
in the Netherlands,
you do so on canals...
Why the Netherlands?
The book's about Italy, isn't it?
It's a travel book.
From the Netherlands
via Germany
and here, Switzerland,
all the way to Italy.
Why can you read?
Because I learned it.
From your mother?
My mother has passed away.
Brother Medicus taught me.
I need to be able to read.
I want to become a nurse.
You're already a good nurse.
I know.
Shall we go on?
Let's go on!
But in winter, the canals mark...
Great!
Barry!
And so they were buried...
The paths are not equally safe.
Barry!
Now you want to play?
Do you want to play?
Aosta.
Look, Barry!
There's the sea.
And persuaded him by much coaxing
to guide us to the island.
Avalanche!
I'm coming with you!
I can help!
Julien!
We need all hands on deck.
Fine. Go on.
Where did the avalanche come down?
Further down,
on the Italian side.
Julien, look! There!
Search, Bella!
Yes!
Here?
Here is something!
Search!
Look!
-Schnell!
-Here!
Here!
Give me a hand!
I've got him.
Help pulling!
Slowly. Be careful!
Pull!
I've got him!
He's alive.
Blanket!
Are you alright?
Can you talk to me?
Thans. Thank you very much.
Well done!
How many people are injured?
I don't know!
You'll have to ask Resi.
Certainly not!
George, you know where to put it.
Here he comes.
Who let him out?
I'll take care of the dogs.
You're off duty.
George?
Well done.
We can use you up here.
That country bumpkin's
so full of himself.
Come on. Go now!
Why? He hasn't harmed me.
No one will find out that it was you.
But I don't want to!
Since when do you get to decide
what you want or don't want?
Coward!
Get off me, get off!
What are you doing?
Julien!
George stole the dog!
He hid it in his room!
It was George!
Where have you come from?
George stole the dog!
It is the Lord's will
that His creatures must die.
And it is His will
when it should happen.
This applies to us humans.
But it also applies to animals.
That's not true, Prior.
Oh, it isn't?
If...
If someone is in distress and...
and we can help,
then that's also God's will, isn't it?
You said that we're here to serve.
I didn't just feel sorry for him.
Well, yes, that too.
I felt sorry for him
when Stella didn't feed him.
But he'll help a lot of people
when he grows up.
George.
Brother Benedict told me
that you stole this book
from the library.
What did you want to do with it?
Answer!
I wanted it so I could learn to read.
Alright, then read.
When the sea was very rough,
we came to a gondolier
who was trying to pull his boat
out of the waves
and we compelled him...
Okay. I think we got it.
The dog will immediately
return to the barn,
where it belongs, with its own kind.
Barry.
The dog's name's Barry.
Barry...
And you won't commit another offence.
Do you understand?
Yes, Prior.
Brother Benedict...
From now on, George will participate
in studies with the novices.
Prior...!
And do give him some decent clothes!
You're right, George.
We're here to serve.
You lied to me.
I didn't lie to you.
I just didn't tell you everything.
When did we stop
telling each other everything?
Resi.
What's wrong, darling?
I don't like being alone all the time.
You're not alone.
Except for Pietro,
the monks don't talk with me.
And the stupid novices...
They just look down on me,
except when they have a scratch
and need some ointment.
And you...
You're always working,
in the stable or in the mountains.
And in the evening,
when you come home, you're tired.
Of course I'm alone.
Ever since we've been here...
Since Mom passed away.
And now George is here
and I get on well with him.
You two...
You really had me fooled.
And you even got a place at school.
I want you to keep training Barry.
Come on, get in there!
Did you hear that, Barry?
Listen carefully to what George
is going to tell you.
I'll make a good dog out of you.
You've done a good job.
And I ate well.
Of course!
Study well and don't
be afraid of the novices.
Oh no...!
Gentlemen.
He's supposed to be a novice now?
Can a cow dance?
Barry!
Heavens above!
I haven't got time now.
I'll come back to you after school.
Gentlemen!
Silence.
Gentlemen.
Come here, Barry, come!
Come!
Sit, Barry!
You have to obey now, Barry.
Heavens above.
Like a stork with a twisted beak.
Go on.
George!
Would you like to try?
Yes, good.
You can sit on a cushion.
This is a Moroccan tagine with lemon.
How are things going at school?
Heavens above!
Do you want to be a teacher too?
They're all so clever.
Would you like to come too?
Ask the prior.
A girl among the novices.
They" all become monks one day.
And anyway, what would I do
among these clever monkeys?
Soon you'll be one of them.
I won't!
Yes, you will!
No, I won't!
You can sleep at night.
Listen. you have to work
especially hard
otherwise you'll always be a farm boy.
Do you understand?
-It's over, I won!
-Yeah...
That's right, you cheated!
What have we learned, Barry?
Come!
Turn around, follow me.
And now, sit!
Well done!
-Come, Bella. Come.
-Barry, come.
Hey! Good man,
You shouldn't rest here.
My son is in Switzerland.
Have to cross the pass.
Come.
Get some soup from the kitchen! Go on!
-Hurry!
-Come, Barry!
Hot!
Don't spill everything on the table!
Watch out!
I don't have time!
No time!
No, Barry, wait!
Is there anything left in the bottle?
I'm sorry.
That mustn't happen to you again!
Come on!
Come, Barry!
What's he doing?
He doesn't seem to be hungry.
Barry, come to me.
Just try it on. Come on!
If it doesn't fit,
I'll take it off again.
Very good.
What do you think, Barry?
Now the soup can't spill anymore.
Even if the rescuers are slow
or get stuck somewhere.
Or stumble, like I did.
Yes, Barry.
George?
For you.
For me?
From Italy.
Dear George,
A comrade is writing this letter for me.
Perhaps a monk will read it to you.
I hope the stone snail
has brought you luck.
I'm sorry I couldn't stay with you.
Imagine,
the Austrians promised me more pay
than the two of us can earn in a year.
As a soldier, I got boots and a gun.
We're waiting for the war to start
against the French.
We have lots of time and little food.
When the war is over,
I'll come and get you.
Alfons.
George.
We'll show him
what we're capable of.
What's going on?
What's this?
Give it back.
-Oh, a love letter!
-Give it back!
Give it back!
Oh! From the brave soldier
who abandoned you.
My family's none of your business.
A soldier in the Austrian army...
That's what you call family?
And where's your family?
Why are you up here?
My family...
My family pays for everything here.
You're being fed here
thanks to my family.
That you don't have to sleep in a pigsty
is thanks to my family.
You country bumpkin!
Is spring finally coming?
The spring storms will come first.
The worst of the cold weather is over.
But the avalanches...
Stay together.
The snow's unpredictable
when it gets warmer.
But he can become quite unpleasant.
If Brother Benedict gives you a mean
look, the class immediately freezes.
But he's a nice teacher as long as...
Hey! A wolf.
A wolf!
Go behind the rocks!
Barry! Come back here.
Come on, George!
-Leave the dog alone!
-Barry!
Come back!
Come on, George!
He won't harm us.
George.
-Everything okay?
-George!
Well done, Barry!
-George, everything okay?
-Yes.
-How did you do this?
-What did you do?
No, how did you do that?
I don't know.
You know that this was dangerous,
what you did up there.
We trusted each other.
You've made a good dog out of him.
He's the best!
For you.
Thank you.
I prayed that something would happen.
-Like that a rock would fall on the wolf.
-And suddenly...
it became dead quiet.
George and Barry... they just
stood there, in front of a wolf.
-A real wolf?
-The atmosphere was very strange.
George! Come over here.
So small, but so brave!
I almost wet my pants.
I'd never have dared to do that.
The French are coming!
Napoleon's soldiers!
A little dignity, gentlemen. Dignity!
Good evening, captain.
Welcome to our hospice.
How many soldiers are you?
For the moment just my section.
But others will come.
How can you even talk to them?
In French.
It doesn't matter where they're from.
We're giving them shelter.
That's what the hospice is for.
But they're soldiers.
Frenchmen!
They destroy everything in their path.
Your brother's a soldier too.
Alfons is out there
and he's going to fight the French.
And I don't know if he...
He doesn't have the stone snail anymore.
It always brought him luck.
Now I have it.
He'll run away if it gets dangerous.
Do you think so?
Yes. He runs away and comes back to you.
Everything will be fine.
We have to leave at dawn
otherwise we won't get to the wedding
in Italy by daylight.
That's Celestin's father,
Mr von Wydler,
and his sister,
Miss Florence.
Tomorrow, everyone will
travel on to Italy for a wedding.
Celestin too?
...out there in the wild valleys,
in wind and weather.
Just a few days ago
we rescued a group of poor pilgrims,
when suddenly
a huge wolf stood in front of me.
A huge animal with bulging eyes
and enormous teeth.
I ordered Barry to stand with me
in front of the wolf.
The wolf was so confused,
that he tucked his tail between his legs
and ran away.
You should have seen that.
Would you like to see Barry?
Father, may I go with him?
If Brother Benedict allows you to.
He has relieved me of my duties.
Hey, you fool!
I'm sorry!
Hurry up and clean that up!
Move. Come on! Get up!
-You're hurting him!
-You have to show them who's boss.
That's the only way they'll obey.
Stupid animal!
Sit! Off!
Get out!
Come on, Florence!
Let's leave this country bumpkin.
Are you alright?
-Do you want to pet him?
-Is he...
-May I?
-Yes.
He's very well-behaved!
Barry's the best dog in the world.
If I had a dog,
I'd never hit it.
It would have to be just like Barry.
We'd be friends, you and me.
Best friends.
Why do you need that?
For the journey.
Where is he?
I couldn't do anything, George.
Where's Barry?
In the stable,
with the soldiers.
He's going with Florence tomorrow.
He belongs here!
In the mountains!
Von Wydler is an influential man.
Florence will take good care of him.
You don't know that!
They may not take Barry away.
George, choose another dog.
No!
George!
Pietro!
Barry.
Let's go away.
But you have to be quiet.
Barry.
Quiet.
Come.
Sit!
Wait!
They want to take him away from me.
And where are you going now?
They won't take you back.
I'm going to Alfons.
Into war?
I don't want you to...
not be here anymore.
I have to go, Resi.
Do you have your lucky charm?
The stone snail?
Take care of yourself.
Goodbye, Barry.
Barry, come!
We're almost there, Barry.
We just have to make it to the hut.
Come, get in here!
We'll be safe here until tomorrow.
I know you're hungry too!
Everything's fine.
Look, Barry. This...
is Verona.
Alfons is here.
And we're here, in Switzerland.
With a few big jumps
we'll be there.
And if there's not too
much snow in Italy,
we'll manage to get there in ten days.
It's madness to set off in this fog!
I told them to wait another day.
But Mr von Wydler wouldn't listen.
Damn!
Barry, we overslept.
Barry, don't pull so hard!
Hey, what's the matter?
Barry!
Barry, here you are!
You?
Where are the others?
Florence, and your father?
Did he abandon you here?
Certainly not, you idiot!
Come on!
No!
I'm staying here!
They'll find me.
I'm Celestin von Wydler.
You're nobody out here.
Do you understand?
Come on,
I'll help you get down to the valley.
Leave me alone!
I'm not afraid!
Fine, we'll go on to Italy without you.
Barry.
Come on, Barry, let's go.
Is this even the right way?
You have no idea where we are!
I knew it was you.
Who stole the animal.
You mean Barry, who found you?
We're lost!
You and your damn dog.
We need shelter from the storm.
We have to trust Barry!
I can't go on! My leg.
It's too much.
Come on!
Pull yourself together!
Well done, Barry!
Go ahead. I'll be right there!
Where are you going?
Keep going, Barry.
Are you crazy? The book's valuable!
Would you rather freeze to death?
Where are we?
Somewhere under a glacier.
That was your idea,
about Barry.
Florence would have taken
good care of him.
I know that.
But you wanted to take
Barry away from me.
Even though you already have everything.
You have got everything!
Everyone likes you.
Julien, Resi
and you're good with the dogs.
Even Matteo is now your friend.
Since you've arrived...
everyone has begun... to shine.
Why didn't you turn back
when the storm started?
My father said that the weather
would get better in the valley.
And the porters didn't say anything?
They didn't resist?
You don't know my father.
My father only sees his business
and Florence with her pretty face.
And my brother,
with his fiancée in Milan.
I wouldn't want to see myself either.
An ugly weakling with a crippled leg.
You're not ugly.
Only when you're mean.
Barry.
Celestin doesn't make it to the valley.
We have to go back to the hospice.
And when we get back,
we can no longer be together.
Then you have to go with Florence.
My father will never find us here.
Right?
No one will find us in here.
Barry!
Come!
This has to lead somewhere.
But look...
We can't even really stand.
How are you going to climb down there?
With all that ice?
Not climbing...
Are you scared?
Of course!
Me too.
One...
two...
Barry!
Come, Barry.
Thanks!
Look!
I can't go on.
Come on!
We're almost there.
It's not far now.
You can hold on to Barry.
Holy Mother of God!
Help!
Celestin!
My son!
Help!
Dad.
George!
Thank God!
Hang in there!
Everything will be fine.
I'm so glad you're back!
You've only got a sprained foot
and a few frostbitten toes.
Where's Barry?
This is a hospital room, you idiot!
Sorry.
I have to take George to the prior.
Now?
Mr von Wydler and his daughter
want to continue their journey.
I hear you're well.
I'm glad to hear it.
You stole, George.
And from a patron of
the monastery at that.
What do you have to say about that?
I didn't want Barry
to have to live in a town.
I wanted him to stay up here.
You broke the rules again.
Prior, with all due respect.
George saved his comrade's life.
Yes.
You have shown courage and humanity.
I therefore refrain from punishment.
May I...
say goodbye to Barry?
George.
You brought back my son.
I can't thank you enough for that.
So...
Barry belongs to you.
And you belong to him.
I'm sorry I wanted to take him away
from you.
Thank you.
One more thing, George.
We've decided to accept you as a novice.
Mr von Wydler will cover the costs
of your education.
In three years you can join the Order
and become a priest.
I don't want to become a priest.
Heavens above... George!
I'd like to teach
the children in my village
everything I've learned here at school.
You want to become a teacher?
Well...
Well.
That should be fine with our rules,
that you continue to attend classes
with us
and become a good teacher.
Barry! Hello!
Hello.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Come, Celestin.
-Yes, Barry.
-A fine dog.
-Barry, you're the best dog in the world!
-You're such a good dog.
Did you miss me already?
George?
Alfons!
Is the war over?
I don't know.
But it's not my war anymore.
-This is Resi.
-Hello.
-This is Celestin.
And this
is my friend Barry.
I told you he was going to run away.
Come!
I'll take you to Brother Pietro
in the kitchen.
We won't let your brother go hungry.
Enjoy your meal.
Do you think I can rest for a bit here?
Before we set off on our way?
On our way?
Home, to the farm.
We'll rebuild it.
I'm staying here.
What?
You want to stay up here?
There's nothing here!
Just snow and ice!
I'm going to school here.
With the novices.
And I'll make sure he stays well-behaved
and focused!
I will follow you to our village,
as soon as I've become a teacher.
George the teacher...
I always knew you'd turn out to be
a remarkable person.
It brings good luck, doesn't it?
The stone snail?
Actually, it's not a stone snail,
it's an ammonite.
Nerd!
Do you think others
will also return to the village?
We'll see.
-They won't all have become rich abroad.
-Like you, you mean?
Hey!
First,
I'll rebuild the stable.
I can shelter with the animals.
And next winter, I'll rebuild the house.
And then you'll soon be home.
Are you sure?
I have everything I need.
See you soon.
And you,
take care of my brother.
Take good care of him, alright?
Come, Barry.
Alfons!
When I'm a teacher, I'll come home.
BARRY LIVED FROM 1800 TO 1814.
HE RESCUED THE LIVES OF 40 PEOPLE.